# **Vitaliy Kozakevich**



Khmelnytskyi

#### **Profile**

I am an open-minded person, who is highly motivated and passionate about web development. During my studies at university, I got experience in the basics of computer sciences and decided to further develop my skills in these sectors. Active team member with leadership skills.

	Skills	
CSS		• • • •
Redux		• • • • •
HTML5		• • • •
React		• • • •
Git		• • • •
JavaScript		• • • •
Jira		• • • • •
AJAX		• • • •
PugJS		• • • •
	Languages	
<b>Ukrainian</b> Native	_	
<b>English</b> Upper-Intermediate	_	
Russian	_	

## **Professional Experience**

**Frontend Developer,** *UpWork* May 2023 – present Development of web applications.

**Frontend Developer,** *Dev Smile* Sep 2022 – May 2023 Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine The platform allows a user to create/edit web sites, online shops, works with templates, etc. Also, this project is a minimally viable product that was developed on the basis of a ready-made solution for bots.

**Frontend Developer,** *Dev Smile* Apr 2022 – Sep 2022 Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine A platform enables clients to easily develop/publish chatbots to web apps, and chat services such as Telegram, Viber, Facebook Messenger, and other popular channels. The platform gives you tools and modules to easily build a chat bot with any complexity: question-answer; integration with third-party services, etc.

## **Education**

## Master of CS,

Khmelnytskyi National University Sep 2022 – present Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine

### **Courses**

**Front-end Development course** 

Sep 2021 – Nov 2021 Khmelnytskyi

#### Interests

Hobbyhorsing